Guide to the Leonard Solomon Silk papers, 1929-1995 and undated, bulk 1950-1985 RL.01187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 6096, 1933-1985, and undated, 86 boxes
  - Press Releases (Box 51)
    - Congress of the United States, Joint Economic Committee, for release April 25, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Data Resources, Inc., Press Release, for release June 14, 1970 (Box 51)
    - Embassy of Japan, Japan's Ambassador Stresses Role for Japan in Assisting Lesser Developed Asian Countries, for release after March 15, 1971, 4:00 p.m. EST (Box 51)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, Monthly Review, May 1973, for release May 10, 1973 (Box 51)
    - First National City Bank, Monthly Economic Letter, May 1971, release May 10, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, Lockheed Accepts $200 Million Imposed C-5A Loss in Resolving its Disputes, for immediate release (Box 51)
    - Senator Walter F. Mondale, The Future of American Trade Policies, for release Jan. 1, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York, for release May 25, 1972 (Box 51)
    - Michael W. Moynihan, News Release, Kendall Warns of World Trade Bloc Hurting U.S. Exports, for release Feb. 24, 1971 (Box 51)
    - National Industrial Conference Board, The Outlook for Capital Goods, An Address by James W. Knowles, Director of Research, Joint Economic Committee, U.S. Congress, for release May 7, 1970 (Box 51)
    - National Planning Association, for release March 15 and April 28, 1971, 2 pieces (Box 51)
    - New York Stock Exchange, Inc., Summary of Address by Dr. William C. Freund, What's Ahead for American Business? for release March 21, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Organisation of Economic Co-Operation and Development, O.E.C.D. Press Release, Nov. 19, 1970 (Box 51)
    - Public Interest Economics Center, Economists Speak Out on the Administration's Budget for Fiscal Year 1974 and on National Priorities, for release June 5, 1973 (Box 51)
    - Sherwood Ross Associates Inc., for immediate release, Dec. 9, 1972 and Jan. 6, 1973 (Box 51)
    - Taxation with Representation, Controversy Over Tax Writen-off Plan Continues, for release April 30, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Philip H. Trezise, Address by Trezise, Assistant Secretary of State for Economic Affairs, for release Dec. 29, 1970 (Box 51)
    - The University of Chicago, immediate release, Sept. 18, 1970 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce, Commerce News, for immediate release, Aug. 13, 1970 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce, Commerce News, Census Bureau Publishes School Booklet on American Women, for release May 25, 1973 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, News, Union Wage Rates of Building Trades Workers Rise 1.1 Percent During First Quarter of 1970, for release May 7, 1971 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, News, The Employment Situation: July 1970, for release Jan. 5, 1973 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, News, The Employment Situation: December 1972, for release Jan. 5, 1973 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, News, Major Collective Bargaining Settlements, 1970, for release Jan. 29, 1971 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Department of the Treasury, News, Statement of the Honorable David M. Kennedy, Secretary of the Treasury, Before the Joint Economic Committee, July 21, 1970, for release upon delivery (Box 51)
    - Weeden and Company, for immediate release, Oct. 12 and Nov. 10, 1972 (Box 51)
    - White, Weld and Company, Inc., News, Investment Firm Economists See Long-Term Interest Rates Declining in 1973, for immediate release (Box 51)
    - Dean Witter and Company, Inc., Positive Investment Policy - David A. Baker, Senior Vice President and Research Director wrote the section of this report titled, What Will we do for the Encore? for immediate release, May 18, 1971 (Box 51)
  - Reprints (Box 51)
    - Boulding, K. E., Reprinted for Challenge, July-Aug. 1966, pp. 5-7 (Box 51)
    - Business Week Reports On: Business Forecasting, Reprinted from Sept. 24, 1955 issue, pp. 2-10, 2 copies (Box 51)
    - Cohen, K. J. and Cyert, R. M., Computer Models in Dynamic Economics, Graduate School of Industrial Administration Reprint No. 68, Carnegie Institute of Technology, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, Reprinted from the Quarterly Journal of Economics, Vol. LXXV, Feb. 1961, pp. 112-127 (Box 51)
    - Cyert, R.M., Feigenbaum, E.A., and March, J.G., Models in a Behavioral Theory of the Firm, Graduate School of Industrial Administration Reprint No. 31, Carnegie Institute of Technology, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, Reprinted from Behavior Science, Vol. 4, No. 2, April 1959, pp. 81-95 (Box 51)
    - Gruber, W. H., Step-By-Step Management Innovation, Reprinted from Management Adviser, March-April 1972, pages not indicated (Box 51)
    - " and Niles, J. S., Problems in the Utilization on Management Science/Operations Research: A State of the Art Survey, Reprinted from The Bulletin of the Institute of Management Sciences, Vol. 2, No. 1, Nov. 1971, pp. 12-19 (Box 51)
    - Henderson, H., The Limits of Traditional Economics: New Models for Managing a 'Steady State Economy,' Reprinted from Financial Analysists Journal, May-June 1973, pp.1-10 (Box 51)
    - Leff, N. H., Investment in the LDCs: The Next Wave, Reprinted from Columbia Journal of World Business, Vol. IV, No. 6, Nov.-Dec. 1969, pages not indicated (Box 51)
    - Lekachman, R., Quarrels Among the Economists, Reprinted from Harper's Magazine, Oct. 1967, pp. 1-10 (Box 51)
    - Manning, E. M., Editor-in-Chief, The Third Dimension of the Fourth Estate, Reprinted from Finance Magazine, April 1973, pages not indicated (Box 51)
    - Miller, W. L., Herbert Spencer's Theory of Welfare and Public Policy, Reprinted from The History of Political Economy, Vol. 4, No. 1, Spring 1972, pp. 207-231 (Box 51)
    - The New York Times, Breaking Down Job Walls, Editorial Appearing in The New York Times, Feb. 12, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Pechman, J. A., The Rich, The Poor, and the Taxes They Pay, The Brookings Institution, Reprint 168 reprinted from The Public Interest, No. 17, Fall 1969, pp. 21-43 (Box 51)
    - Schott, F. H., The Interest Rate Outlook, Reprinted from Nation's Business, Dec. 1971, page not indicated (Box 51)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Business Power, Today and Tomorrow, Reprinted from Daedalus, Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Vol. 98, No. 1, of the Proceedings of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, pp. 174-190, 2 copies, also two copies from the Tuck School Issue of Daedalus (Box 51)
    - The Research Revolution and Its Economic Implications, reprinted from Social Science, Vol. 37, No. 1, Jan. 1962, pp. 24-34 (Box 51)
    - The Role of the Business Corporation in the Economy and Society, Reprinted from Economic Systems and Public Policy: Essays in Honor of Calvin Bryce Hoover, Robert. S. Smith and Frank T. Devyver, eds. 1966, pp. 83-103 (Box 51)
    - Thorelli, H. B., The Political Economy of the Firm, Basis for a New Theory of Competition?, Reprinted from Address at the Annual Meeting of the Schweizerische Gesellschaft fur Statistik und Volkswirtschaft, May 28, 1965, at St. Gallen, pp. 248-262 (Box 51)
  - Reports (Box 51)
    - Allen, J. H., McGraw-Hill Special Report, The Problem, Business and the Urban Crisis, 1968 (Box 51)
    - Chamberlain, N. W., Columbia University in the City of New York, Social Impact of the New Technology, 110th Session - Annual Report, Oct. 17, 1967 (Box 51)
    - Editorial Research Reports, Jan. 12, Feb. 3, Feb 9. and April 27, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust by line, Aug. 1970 (Box 51)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Chairman, The National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, Inc., Report of the Task Force on Employment, June 30, 1969, 7 items (Box 51)
    - The National Industrial Conference Board, Report of Group I: Silk (Chairman, Barber, Bock, Fubini, Zadeh - The Information Process), undated (Box 51)
    - Public Interest Economic Center, First Semi-Annual Report of the Public Interest Economics Center, Dec. 1972, and Ninety-Day Supplement to the First Semi-Annual report of the Public Interest Economics Center, April 1973 (Box 51)
    - Report of the Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System on Ways to Moderate Fluctuations in the Construction of Housing, undated (Box 51)
    - Weeden and Company, Annual Report, for the year ended Sept. 30, 1971, and Jan. 10, 1972 (Box 51)
  - Resumes and Biographical Sketches (Box 51)
    - Bower, Richard S., Amos Tuck School, Hanover, New Hampshire (Box 51)
    - Gruber, William H., Research and Planning Institute, Inc (Box 51)
    - Kemeny, John G., Professor of Mathematics, Dartmouth College (Box 51)
    - Luehrmann, Arthur W., University of California at Irvine (Box 51)
    - Menge, John A., Associate Professor of Economics, Dartmouth College (Box 51)
    - Piatkowski, Thomas F (Box 51)
    - Quinn, James Brian, New Products Analyst, Allen B. DuMont Laboratories, Inc (Box 51)
    - Schwartzman, David, Department of Economics, New School (Box 51)
    - Williamson, J. Peter, The Amos Tuck School, Hanover, New Hampshire (Box 51)
  - Seminars (Box 51)
    - The Brookings Institution, economic research seminar announcement, July 16, 1969 (Box 51)
    - Columbia Faculty Peace Action, War, Peace and the Economy, May 1st (Box 51)
    - Seminar in Public Policy, Reading Lists and General Information, 1965 (Box 51)
  - Speeches, Statements and Remarks (Box 51)
    - Baranson, J., Multinational Corporations and Developing Country Goals for Technological Self-Sufficiency, Allied Social Science Associations, 1972, Meetings in Toronto, Canada, Dec. 28-30, Dec. 27, 1972, mimeograph, 19 pages (Box 51)
    - Biemiller, A. J., Director, Department of Legislation, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, Statement before The House Committee on Banking and Currency, on The National Defense Production Act, June 18, 1970, mimeograph, 13 pages (Box 51)
    - Statement before the House Committee on Foreign Affairs, Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy, On Trade Adjustment Assistance, April 25, 1972, mimeograph, 15 pages (Box 51)
    - Boulding, K. E., After Samuelson, Who Needs Adam Smith? Presentation at the American Economic Association Annual Meeting, Detroit, Dec. 30, 1970, mimeograph, 20 pages (Box 51)
    - Brimmer, A. F., Economic Policy and the Restoration of Price Stability in the United States, remarks before the Annual Convention of the Vermont Bankers Association, Manchester, Vermont, June 20, 1970, mimeograph, 13 pages (Box 51)
    - Burns, A., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, July 23, 1970, mimeograph, 19 pages (Box 51)
    - The Basis for Lasting Prosperity, Address in the Pepperdine College Great Issues Series at the Beverly Hilton Hotel, Los Angeles, California, Dec. 7, 1970, mimeograph, 25 pages (Box 51)
    - Cook, G. B., The Central Market System: Putting the Markets to Work for the Investor, address presented at the New York Financial Writers' Association, Americana Hotel, New York, March 15, 1973, mimeograph, 21 pages (Box 51)
    - Costanzo, G. A., Toward International Monetary Reform, remarks of 1972 Annual Meetings of the World Bank and International Monetary Fund, New York, published in pamphlet form, Oct 2, 1972 (Box 51)
    - President Driscoll's remarks introducing Leonard S. Silk as Commencement Speaker at Commencement Exercises, South-eastern Massachusetts Technological Institute, North Dartmouth, Nov. 9, 1967, typed, 2 pages (Box 51)
    - Eckstein, O., The Economic Outlook: A Trip Through the Chamber of Horrors, Before the International Purchasing Conference of the National Association of Purchasing Management, Boston, May 20, 1970, xerox, 11 pages (Box 51)
    - Stretched Recession, before the Twelfth Annual Forecasting Conference, American Statistical Association, New York Chapter, April 30, 1970, mimeograph, 2 copies, 14 pages (Box 51)
    - Fowler, H. H., Remarks at the Conference Board Seminar, April 25, 1971, mimeograph, 34 pages (Box 51)
    - Holt, C. C., et. al, Manpower Approach Needed to Deal with Unemployment-Inflation Dilemma, undated, mimeograph, 8 pages (Box 51)
    - Homer, S., The Bond Market in a Changing World, A Talk delivered before the Boston Economic Club, May 5, 1971, mimeograph, 10 pages (Box 51)
    - Structural Changes in the American Bond Market, a talk delivered in Bellagio, Italy at the International Investment Symposium of P. N. Kemp-Gee and Company, London, June 3, 1970, mimeograph, 19 pages (Box 51)
    - Jha, L. K., International Trade and Payment System - Need for a Fresh Look, Address to the Economic Club of New York, May 4, year unknown, carbon, 11 pages (Box 51)
    - Johnston, G. S., Statement before the Securities and Exchange Commission, Public Investigatory Hearing on Structure of the Securities Markets, Nov. 18, 1971, types, 7 pages (Box 51)
    - Kaufman, H., The Prospects for Interest Rates and Liquidity, address before an investment and properties studies conference, Oct. 28, 1970, mimeograph, 13 pages (Box 51)
    - Is the United States in a Two-Year Financial Cycle? address before the Annual General Meeting of the Association of International Bond Dela Dealers, Hotel Inter-Continental, Paris, France, April 16, 1971, mimeograph, 15 (Box 51)
    - Statement before the Joint Economic Committee of the Congress of the United States, Washington, D.C., July 9, 1970, mimeograph, 15 pages (Box 51)
    - Kendall, D. M., Toward a Positive Trade Policy: Negotiate Now, Address to the 34th Mid America World Trade Conference, LaSalle Hotel, Chicago, Feb. 24, 1971, mimeograph, 14 pages (Box 51)
    - Mann, M., Remarks before the Financial Analysts Federation, 24th Annual Conference, Controlling Inflation: Policies and Prospects, Cleveland, Ohio, May 17, 1971, mimeograph, 10 pages (Box 51)
    - Minsky, H. P., Economic Issues in 1972: A Perspective, a presentation to a symposium on the economics of the candidates sponsored by the department of economics of Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, Oct. 6, 1972, mimeograph, 7 pages (Box 51)
    - The National Assembly, Position Statement on Racial Discrimination in the Construction Industry, Dec. 10, 1970, mimeograph, 2 pages (Box 51)
    - Okun, A. M., Excerpts from the Economic Outlook and National Economic Policy, prepared for the Twentieth Annual Business Economists Conference of the Graduate School of Business, University of Chicago, April 27, 1971, mimeograph, 10 pages (Box 51)
    - Perry, G. L., Inflation and Unemployment, prepared for the Annual Conference on Savings and Residential Financing, May 7-8, 1970, mimeograph, 26 pages (Box 51)
    - Slater, J. E., President, Aspen Institute, Foreword, Progress and Current Status of the Project to Consider An 'Institute for Analyses of Public Choices', Sept. 1, 1972, mimeograph, 46 pages (Box 51)
    - Saulnier, R. J., Is a Tax Increase Inevitable?, Remarks presented at the 24th National Conference of the Tax Foundation, Plaza Hotel, New York, Dec. 5, 1972, mimeograph, 9 pages (Box 51)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Draft Lecture, undated, typed annotated, 2 pages (Box 51)
    - Trueblood, R. M., Who Likes Telling it Like it is? The Time is Now for the APB, Preliminary speaking draft for the 83rd Annual Meeting of the American Institute of CPAs, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, Sept. 22, 1970, mimeograph, 27 pages (Box 51)
    - Ushiba, H. E. Nobuhiko, Ambassador of Japan to the United States, Speech for the Civic Luncheon on the Occasion of a Symposium on "The Opening Door", San Francisco, California, March 15, 1971, mimeograph, 10 pages (Box 51)
    - Warne, C. E., Government Intervention and the Consumer, Address before the Association for Evolutionary Economics, New York City, Dec. 28, 1965, xerox, 6 pages (Box 51)
    - N.A., A Proposed Statement of Relationship Urban Coalition and the National Assembly, undated, mimeograph, 2 pages (Box 51)
    - N.A., U.S. Treasury Statement, undated, xerox, 1 page (Box 51)
    - N.A., The White House Press Conference, undated, carbon, 1 page (Box 51)
  - Tables (Box 51)
    - Domestic Trunks + Pan Am Comparative Earnings 9 Months and 3rd Qtr. 1970 VS 1969, undated, xerox, 18 pages (Box 51)
    - Gross Reserves of National Monetary Authorities, 1949-1970, undated, xerox, 1 page (Box 51)
    - Japan's Balance of Payments in 1973 ($ million, UMF basis), May 17, 1973, xerox, 2 pages (Box 51)
    - The National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, INC., Operating Report from January 1, 1969 to June 30, 1969, undated, xerox, 2 pages (Box 51)
    - Reconciled to May 19 press release, May 20, 1970, xerox, 3 pages (Box 51)
    - Sources, Composition and Distribution of World Reserves: 1937-1970 (in billions of U.S. dollars), April 1971, mimeograph, annotated, 1 page (Box 51)
    - World Military Expenditures 1971 (Errata), undated, typed, 1 page (Box 51)
  - University Course Work/Reading Lists (Box 51)
    - Harvard University, Department of Economics, reading list for Spring 1968-1969, mimeograph, 3 pages (Box 51)
    - Reading List - Economics 140, Market Organization, Behavior, and Public Policy, Fall Term 1968-1969, 7 pages, 2 copies (Box 51)
  - Working Notes, 63 items (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 51)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Application for Employment, the American University, Washington, D.C (Box 51)
    - Chapter 7: A Specific Price and Output Model, based on an unpublished working paper by R.M. Cyert et al, pp. 128-147 (Box 51)
    - Filmstrip Guide, McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc., The United States Geography - Social Studies Series and Communism: What you Should Know about it and why, 2 items (Box 51)
    - Guest Lists, 8 items (Box 51)
    - Income tax for Leonard S. Silk (Box 51)
    - Inflation, a public information film produced by the Committee for Economic Development (Box 51)
    - List of selections for which permission to reprint is sought (Box 51)
    - Map locating Hotel D'Isly in France (Box 51)
    - Print of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 51)
    - Western Union Telegram, dated July 7, 1969 (Box 51)
    - Williamson, O. E., (chapter) 9-A Model of Rational Managerial Behavior, pp. 237-267 (Box 51)
  - Clippings and Articles (Box 82)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Ethics and Profits: The Crisis of Confidence in American Business, 1977 (Box 82)
    - Establishment Power, undated (Box 82)
    - About China, 1977-1979, 3 pages (Box 82)
    - The Economy and Economics, 1971-1978, 13 items (Box 82)
    - undated (Box 82)
    - Italy, 1975 (Box 82)
    - OPEC, 1975 (Box 82)
    - Saudi Arabia, 1975 and undated (Box 82)
    - South Africa, 1974 (Box 82)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1977, 3 items (Box 82)
    - Chinese clipping (Box 82)
  - Correspondence, 28 January 1975 - 12 January 1979 and undated (Box 82)
    Correspondence between Leonard S. Silk and important economists, politicians, and academics such as Jay W. Forrester, Jaroslav Vanek, David Lapin, George Katona, Lincoln Caplan, Alfred Nussbaum, William Kruskal, Harvey Leibenstein, Douglas White, David MacEachron.
  - Documents (Box 85)
    - 86th Congress, 1st session, Committee print, Copyright Law Revision, Studies prepared for the Subcommittee on the Judiciary 1960 (Box 85)
    - 86th Congress, 2nd session, Committee print, Copyright Law Revision, studies prepared for the Subcommittee on Patents Trademarks, and Copyrights, of the Committee of Judiciary, 1960 (Box 85)
    - 94th Congress, 2nd session, Report No. 94-803, The Antitrust Improvements Act of 1979, report of the Committee on the Judiciary United States Senate, part 1, 1976 (Box 85)
    - United Nations Document, E/4942/ST/ECA/141 World Economic Survey, 1969-1970 (Box 85)
  - Drafts (Box 85)
    - International Economic Consequences of High-Priced Energy, Committee for Economic Development, Confidential -- not for release, May 7, 1975 (Box 85)
    - No title, final draft, for JDR remarks on corporate social responsibility, October 19, 1977 (Box 85)
  - Subject Files (Box 85)
    - folders containing: clippings and article, correspondence, interviews, manuscripts, newsletters, outlines, reprints, etc (Box 85)
    - Brookings + AEI Books/North, 12 items (Box 85)
    - Ecom. Education, 1975, 89 items (Box 85)
    - Energy/Carter, 1977, 89 items (Box 85)
  - Subject Files (Box 86)
    - Galbraith/Basic Books, 1973, 48 items (Box 86)
    - Hayek, 1975, 88 items (Box 86)
    - Leonard Silk - MET, 1975-1978, 50 items (Box 86)
      Concerning the Metropolitan Opera.
    - Leontief/Basic Books, 1953-1974, 49 items (Box 86)
    - Leontief/Wassily, 1973, 90 items (Box 86)
  - Guides, Handbooks and Manuals (Box 87)
    - Analyzing Government Regulation, A Resource Guide, Joint Council on Economic Education, Economic-Political Science Series, 1978 (Box 87)
    - Guide du rijksmuseum, Rijksmuseum, Amsterdam, 1964 (Box 87)
    - Instructor's Manual to Accompany, Silk: Contemporary Economics, Principles and Issues, Second Edition, 1975 (Box 87)
    - Social Security Handbook, Research and Review Service of America, Inc., 1967 (Box 87)
    - Silk Interview, undated, 29 pages, original type, annotated (Box 87)
    - Evening Dialogue, The Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, March 28, 1978, 3 pages, mimeo, annotated (Box 87)
  - Lists (Box 87)
    - Brookings Books in print, 1978-1979 (Box 87)
    - Brookings Institution, reprint, General Series, no date (Box 87)
    - Capital Series, topic list, revised, no date (Box 87)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, luncheon, September, 1977, 2 copies (Box 87)
    - Governing Mayor's Luncheon, no date (Box 87)
    - Publications since the start of fiscal year 1974 (Box 87)
    - Saudi Arabia: basic statistics, no date (Box 87)
    - Secretary's plane, 26 April, no year (Box 87)
    - Stag buffet dinner at Villa Taverna, October 1977, in honor of the Secretary of the Treasury, W. Michael Blumenthal (Box 87)
    - Sweden's government, Ministry for Foreign Affairs, Press Department, October 1976 (Box 87)
    - The Third Andreotti Government, September 1977 (Box 87)
    - Visit of Secretary of Commerce, Jaunita M. Kreps to China, May 1979 (Box 87)
  - Manuscripts (Box 87)
    - Meltzer, A. H., Costs of Monetarism, 5 pages, xerox (Box 87)
    - Minsky, H. P., The State of the Economy and Economics, 12 pages, xerox (Box 87)
    - Where did the American Economy and Economics Go Wrong, 30 pages, xerox, annotated (Box 87)
    - Sawhill, J. C., editor, Energy Conservation and Public Policy, 218 pages, xerox (Box 87)
  - Manuscripts (Box 88)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Economics in Plain English (Box 88)
      [Marked Simon and Schuster, 326 pages, original type, heavily annotated, with 471 page copy, many duplicate pages and some missing.]
  - Manuscripts (Box 89)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Ethics in Economics, 8 pages, xerox, annotated (Box 89)
    - What Economists Think, 6 pages, xerox (Box 89)
    - Tetens, T. H., The Road to Treason, 51 pages, xerox (Box 89)
    - Warnecke, S. J., The United States and the European Community: The Changing Political and Economic Context of Trade Relations, 29 pages, xerox (Box 89)
    - No author, Blood and the Marketplace, 5 pages, original type, annotated (Box 89)
    - No author, The Poor Countries, marked chapter 27, 29 pages, xerox (Box 89)
    - No author, no title, 5 pages, xerox, and cut and paste (Box 89)
  - Maps (Box 89)
    - Map of Israel, no date, color (Box 89)
    - Map of Jerusalem, Israel Tour guide for the Ministry of Tourism and the Jerusalem Municipality, 1977, color (Box 89)
    - Maps of Saudi Arabia, color, no date (Box 89)
  - Memos (Box 89)
    - John B. Oakes, 1975 (Box 89)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1975 (Box 89)
    - Leonard Forman, 1976 (Box 89)
    - Fred Andrews, 1977 (Box 89)
    - Terry Dewhurst, 1977 (Box 89)
    - A.O. Sulzberger, 1977 (Box 89)